Obinabo Walter Obinna

I. T EXPERT

Well qualified Full stack Web Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2 years of related experience.

Work History

2022/03 - 2022/10

Full Stack Web Developer

Freelance, Awka.

- Maintained complex technology infrastructure and collaborated with product team to implement new features and strategically plan for future products.
- Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines.
- Developed efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of clients.
- Managed time sensitive updates, including content changes and MySQL database upgrades as necessary.
- Used HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL to develop app solutions.

2021/05 - 2021/08

Internship Student

Honeybee Research Center, Awka.

- Participated in training opportunities regarding bee management practices for pollinator conservation.
- Maintained and managed bee colonies including inspecting bees and harvesting honey.



Contact

Address Awka, Nigeria 420001

Phone 08159043899

Email walterobinabo@gmail. com

GitHub My Portfolio

2019/02 - 2019/11

Graphics Designer

Chinels Technologies, Awka.

- Contributed design ideas in early planning stages with customers and project managers.
- Developed display, marketing and packaging materials to support product branding strategies.
- Contributed ideas that slashed client costs by 15% in 6 months.

2014/11 - 2015/12

Marketer

Evans-Vita Beverages Company LTD , Awka.

- Completed in-depth reviews of market conditions and customer preferences.
- Assisted in creating new email campaigns which increased sales by 15%.

Education

2017/09 - 2022/10

B. Sc. Zoology

Nnamdi Azikiwe University - Awka

2008/09 - 2014/06

West African Senior School Certificate

Igwebuike Grammar School - Awka

Skills

Web Development

HTML5 CSS3

JavaScript / jQuery

PHP Laravel MySQL Git / GitHub

Graphics Design

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe After Effects Figma Adobe XD

Soft Skills

Microsoft Office Email Marketing Wordpress Management Content Creation